export let questionList = [
  {
    question: "Who has fastest air acceleration in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Jigglypuff", "Sonic", "Pichu", "Kirby"],
    correctAnswer: "Jigglypuff",
  },
  {
    question: "Who has highest short hop in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Luigi", "Fox", "Min Min", "Greninja"],
    correctAnswer: 'Greninja',
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the most moves in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Pokemon Trainer", "Hero", "Kazuya", "Pyra and Mythra"],
    correctAnswer: 'Pokemon Trainer',
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the lightest character in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: [ "Squirtle", "Jigglypuff", "Pichu", "Olimar"],
    correctAnswer: 'Pichu',
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the heaviest character in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["King K. Rool", "Bowser", "Donkey Kong", "Ridley"],
    correctAnswer: 'Bowser',
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the longest grab in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Samus", "Min Min", "Olimar", "Young Link"],
    correctAnswer: 'Samus',
  },
  {
    question: "Who's air dodge comes out the fastest in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Fox", "Bayonetta", "Sheik", "Diddy Kong"],
    correctAnswer: 'Bayonetta',
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the fastest walk speed in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Lucina", "Kirby", "Pikachu", "Peach"],
    correctAnswer: 'Lucina',
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the fastest air speed in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Yoshi", "Mewtwo", "Captin Falcon", "Inkling"],
    correctAnswer: 'Yoshi',
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the slowest run speed in Super Smash Bro. Ultimate?",
    potAnswers: ["Incineroar", "Simon", "Ganandorf", "Robin"],
    correctAnswer: 'Incineroar',
  }
];
